quadratec.com 2019-04-06

# Privacy Policy | Quadratec

Quadratec is committed to protecting our customers' privacy. We recognize and respect your need for privacy and security as you visit our site. For each visitor that enters our web site, our web server automatically recognizes and retains the visitor's domain name. Information about page usage is gathered, which allows us to determine overall site usage patterns. While we do not collect identifying information about visitors to our site, we do use Industry Standard tracking software that allows us to collect some generic information to serve you better when viewing our website. The only information we normally collect is as follows: 

  * The web site or search engine that referred you to us (if applicable).
  * How many visitors are on the site at any given time.
  * The date and time the pages were accessed.
  * The page or pages you requested.
  * The Browser Version, screen resolution, etc...

### Providing us with personal information.

There are instances where you may elect to provide us with personal information.   
If you place an order with us, participate in our Monthly Quiz, or fill out our customer feedback form, you are transmitting the information that appears to you in the form or the message. This will typically include information like your name, mailing address, email address, Make, Model and Year of your vehicle and any other information necessary to fulfill your request. You never transmit personally identifying information that you do not enter yourself. And this is always your option; this information cannot be collected unless you specifically elect to send it to us. This information is used internally only for the purpose of fulfilling the request or for contacting you directly and is not given or sold to any other organization. Quadratec.com is not compatible with the "Do not track" feature available in some web browsers. 

### How to contact Quadratec

There are a number of ways you can get assistance including online chat, phone and email. Please refer to our Contact Us page for complete details. 

### How to opt-out of communications

Subscribers can cancel their subscription to the newsletter at any time by clicking the ‘unsusbcribe’ link located at the bottom of all the e-mails sent by Quadratec, without costs other than the transmission costs pursuant to the basic tariffs being incurred in this regard. 

### What do we do with this information?

The information is primarily used to improve our site for the purpose of better serving our valued customers. Occasionally we will use the information to send our customers an e-mail announcement. This e-mail may contain new product introductions and/or exclusive offers specifically tailored for the vehicles they own. For example: We don't want to send you a special deal on a Jeep soft top, if you drive a Cherokee. 

### SSL and Secure Shopping

When you use Quadratec.com, all of the information is transmitted via SSL (Secure Sockets Layer). Quadratec.com uses an SSL Certificate certified by GoDaddy.com, Inc. 

### Consumer Notice if Privacy Policy has changed:

If for any reason we change our Privacy Policy, all active Quadratec customers will receive an email detailing the changes and date when these changes will take effect. 

We hope you find our website useful and informative and are always willing to answer questions and receive suggestions. If you have either, please [e-mail](mailto:webmaster@quadratec.com) the webmaster. Thank you. 

To have further questions answered, please write to: [Privacy@Quadratec.com](mailto:Privacy@Quadratec.com)
